


// My Questions!
const questionList = [
  { 
    question: `What does “Tacking" mean?`,
    choice1: `Change Direction`,
    choice2: `I need a tick tack`, 
    choice3: `Stop the boat`, 
    choice4: `Pull down the sail`,
    answer: `Change Direction`,
    userAnswer: ''
  }, 

  {
    question: `What is the stabilizing protruding structure at the bottom of your sail boat called?`,
    choice1: `Clue`, 
    choice2: `Shorb`, 
    choice3: `Bottom`, 
    choice4: `Keel`,
    answer: `Keel`,
    userAnswer:''
  },
  {
    question: `What does it mean when your boat is faced directly into the wind and your sail is fluffing?`,
    choice1: `In Irons`,
    choice2: `Sandy Bottom`, 
    choice3: `Hauling`, 
    choice4: `Boom`,
    answer: `In Irons`,
    userAnswer:''
  }, 
  {
    question: `What is the nautical term used in sailing shouted by the helmsman when tacking?`,
    choice1: `Here we go!`, 
    choice2: `Helms Alee!`, 
    choice3: `Fortune!`, 
    choice4: `Windward`,
    answer: `Helms Alee!`,
    userAnswer:''
  }, 
  {
    question: `What is the saying sailors use to remember colored buoys when entering the harbor?`,
    choice1: `Green Pristine`, 
    choice2: `Helms Alee`, 
    choice3: `Red, Right, Returning!`, 
    choice4: `Yellow garage`,
    answer: `Red, Right, Returning!`,
    userAnswer:''
  }, 
  {
    question: `What is the term for reducing a boat's sail power or shortening the length of a sail?`,
    choice1: `Rolling`, 
    choice2: `Ralphing`,
    choice3: `Roaring`, 
    choice4: `Reefing`,
    answer: `Reefing`,
    userAnswer:''
  }, 
  {
    question: `What does the phrase “mackerel skies and mares' tails make tall ships fly small sails” mean?`,
    choice1: `Need to reef in the sails (make them smaller) because wind is coming`, 
    choice2: `Walk the plank`, 
    choice3: `I dont know`, 
    choice4: `Helms Alee`,
    answer: `Need to reef in the sails (make them smaller) because wind is coming`,
    userAnswer:''
  }, 
  {
    question: `What is the large heavy metal device attached to a chain used to stop a boat in shallow water called?`,
    choice1: `Boulder`,
    choice2: `Anchor`, 
    choice3: `Ball and chain`, 
    choice4: `Car`,
    answer: `Anchor`,
    userAnswer:''
  }, 
  {
    question: `How do sailors and pirates say hello?`,
    choice1: `Why hello there`,
    choice2: `Splendiferious weather`, 
    choice3: `May I interest you in a spot of tea?`, 
    choice4: `Ahoy!!`,
    answer: `Ahoy!!`,
    userAnswer:''
  },
  {
    question: `What is a boat with two hauls called?`,
    choice1: `Steal Pulpit`,
    choice2: `Duck`,
    choice3: `Catamaran`,
    choice4: `Through haul`,
    answer: `Catamaran`,
    userAnswer:''
  }
  
];